In this module, we covered a lot,
Bu lansmana bir sr ey kapacaz.
a lot of theory, a lot of behind the scenes stuff, a lot of important things you have to know.
Sahnelerin arkasnda bir sr teori, bilmeniz gereken ok nemli eyi ierir.
Now don't be shocked if that is not something you know by heart right now,
imdilik kalpten tandnz bir ey deilse, ok olmayn.
this was a lot of stuff and a lot of theory. It is important though because we're next going to dive
Bu ok eydi ve ok nemli bir teori vard, nk daha sonra ders
into our course project and we're using a lot of the things you learn thus far
projemize dalacaz ve imdiye kadar renmi olduunuz ok ey kullanyoruz.
and therefore it's so important that you understand how it's working behind the scenes.
Ve bu nedenle sahnelerin arkasnda nasl altn anlamanz ok nemlidir.
Feel free to go back to some of the videos from this module.
Bu modlden baz videolara geri dnmekten ekinmeyin.
It's perfectly fine if you need to go through some of them again and again to be sure about how this
alt hakknda bir eyler gncelleme yntemi hakknda emin olmak iin ok iyi bir yol var.
shouldComponentUpdate thing worked, how the lifecycle works for updating
Bazlarnn tekrar tekrar gemesi gerekiyorsa, bileenin gncellenmesi iin nasl bir mr dngs
and don't be afraid of seeing all these concepts,
Ve btn bu kavramlar grme korkmayn.
you might not use them all,
Hepsini kullanamazsnz.
you might only use a few of them. But you get better and better
Sadece birkan kullanabilirsiniz, ancak daha iyi ve daha iyi olursunuz.
the more you learn about that and the more you question the approaches you use.
Bunu ne kadar ok reneceksin ve ne kadar ok yaklam kullanrsan sorarsn.
Maybe there are some advanced concepts you may use like a well-placed high order component or a pure
Belki de iyi yerletirilmi yksek mertebeden bir bileen veya saf bir bileen gibi kullanabileceiniz baz gelimi
component.
kavramlar vardr.
And again, there is a course project into which will dive next where you will also see a lot of the things
var ve dolaysyla neyi ne zaman kullanacanza dair bir his de almanz lazm.
you've learned thus far being used and hence there, you should also get a feeling for when to use what.
Ve tekrar, burada kullanld iin rendiiniz eylerin bir ounu greceiniz bir sonraki derste bir ders projesi
So with that let's dive into the course project and let's see more of these things in a bigger project
Bu yzden ders projesine dalalm ve u ana kadar zerinde altmz bir demo projesinden daha
than the demo project we worked on thus far.
byk bir projede bunlardan daha fazlasn grelim.